{
    "subject": "Warren_Beatty",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Love_Affair__1994_film_",
    "human_readable": "Warren Beatty acted in the film Love Affair (1994).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9380130767822266,
            "question": "Was Warren Beatty involved in any other projects besides acting in Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8747537732124329,
            "question": "What impact did Love Affair (1994) have on Warren Beatty's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8428329825401306,
            "question": "Who directed the film Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.837875485420227,
            "question": "What is the name of the actor who starred in Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6624392867088318,
            "question": "What genre is the film Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6082682609558105,
            "question": "Name some other films starring Warren Beatty."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46417737007141113,
            "question": "How was Love Affair (1994) received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4267134666442871,
            "question": "In what year was the film Love Affair released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38771095871925354,
            "question": "Are there any notable similarities between Love Affair (1994) and other romantic films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.168877512216568,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films from the year 1994?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warren Beatty acted in the film Love Affair (1994).",
            "html": "yago_21516_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable similarities between Love Affair (1994) and other romantic films?",
            "html": "yago_21516_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year was the film Love Affair released?",
            "html": "yago_21516_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was Love Affair (1994) received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "yago_21516_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21516_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Warren Beatty played the role of Mike Gambril, an ex-football star, in the movie Love Affair (1994). Therefore, the triple is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Warren Beatty starred in the 1994 film \"Love Affair\" alongside Annette Bening, which supports the statement that Warren Beatty acted in the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}